



Yesunerdene Jargalsaikhan

O Home: Door 21, Apt. 2, 4 khoroo, Bayangol district, 16052, Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia

Email: <u>yesuuygls@gmail.com</u> **\ Phone:** (+976) 99401008 **A Phone:** (+976) 96891008

★ Website: https://yesunerdene.github.io/yesunerdene/
Viber: +97699401008

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/yesunerdene-jargalsaikhan-b46398162/

← Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/Yesunerdene9

Gender: Female **Date of birth:** 09/09/1999 **Nationality:** Mongolian

ABOUT ME

Passionate software engineer, especially experienced in mobile application development for 3.5 years and other software development in the IT industry in Mongolia. Professional at the whole mobile application development process from the blank project to release and launch to public application stores and the maintenance, which includes designing, developing and testing. And I'm very keen to study advanced computer science, especially artificial intelligence and data science.

EDUCATION AND TRAIN-

ING

[01/09/2016 - 01/06/2020]

Bachelor degree in Software Engineering

National University of Mongolia, School of Engineering and Applied Science www.num.edu.mn/en/

Address: 14200, Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia

Final grade: GPA 3.5 / 4.0 Number of credits: 122

Thesis: The real estate advertisement for renting or selling platform based on a map. Based on the thesis, I developed a mobile application and a website for a real estate platform.

Graduated from the **Department of Information and Computer science**

DIGITAL SKILLS

Framework & Technologies

React Native JS | React JS | Symfony (PHP) | Laravel (PHP)

Programming and scripting languages

C | C++ | Java | JavaScript | PHP | HTML | CSS

DBMS, Query languagee

MySQL | MSSQL | GrapgQL

Git

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Mongolian

Other language(s):

English IELTS 6.5

LISTENING C1 READING B2 WRITING B2

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B2 SPOKEN INTERACTION B2

Russian

LISTENING A1 READING A1 WRITING A1

SPOKEN PRODUCTION A1 SPOKEN INTERACTION A1

WORK EXPERIENCE

[10/01/2022 - Current] **Software engineer**

Octagon LLC



City: Ulaanbaatar Country: Mongolia

Octagon LLC is a technology company founded in December 2021 which runs the **Octagon** - a crypto-based NFT marketplace and crypto exchange platform.

I have been working as a software engineer, especially in the mobile application development of the Octagon app, which includes features of a digital wallet control, a crypto exchange and an NFT marketplace. As a developer, I take responsibility for the whole mobile application project, which I do project planning, designing, developing, testing and maintaining the app.

[01/02/2021 - Current] Software engineer

Powered LLC

City: Ulaanbaatar Country: Mongolia

Powered LLC is a technology company founded in January 2021 which runs the YESH.MN - testbased learning app for university general entrance examination for high school students.

I have been working as a software engineer, especially in the mobile application development of YE **SH.MN** app, which includes features for taking a test of entrance exam. I take responsibility for the whole mobile application project, which involves project planning, designing, developing, testing and maintaining the app.

[16/09/2019 - 01/01/2022] **Software engineer**

Digital Mall LLC

Digital Mall LLC is a technology company founded in June 2019 which runs the BananaMall - an ecommerce platform that for online shopping with delivery service.

At the beginning of my 4th year of study in software engineering, my former internship employer company offered me to work as a software developer in their e-commerce system. As a part of the development team, I worked as a software engineer, especially in the development of the mobile application, core backend development, and admin panel of the e-commerce platform, and took responsibility for database engineering.

[01/07/2020 – Current]

Software engineer

Alpha Labs LLC

City: Ulaanbaatar Country: Mongolia

Alpha Labs LLC is a technology company founded in January 2015 and conducts the development of various kinds of platforms.

I have been working as a software engineer, especially in the mobile application development of BS B.MN, G-Power monitoring and ISU Mongolia. I take responsibility in whole projects of the mobile applications respectively, in which I do project planning, designing, developing, testing and maintaining the app.

VOLUNTEERING

[22/07/2019 – 23/08/2019] Internship at And Systems LLC Ulaanbaatar

Worked as an intern, and a software developer at a technology company.

During the internship, I developed:

- Sms notification service in python
- Dynamic create-able survey form platform in *Symfony(PHP)*

PROJECTS

[01/01/2022 - Current] **Octagon Wallet**

Mobile application of Octagon crypto exchange, digital wallet control and NFT marketplace.



Released the mobile application in 2022.03.10 into both App store and Google Play store.

[10/02/2021 - Current] YESH.MN

Mobile application of YESH.MN - test-based learning app for university general entrance examination for high school students.

Released the mobile application in 2021.05.27 into both App store and Google Play store.

[16/09/2019 - 01/01/2022] Bananamall

Mobile application of BananaMall for e-commerce of online shopping and delivery service.

Released the ecommerce website https://bananamall.mn in Novemyber 2019

Released the mobile application in 2021.11.01 into both App store and Google Play store.

[01/07/2020 - 01/01/2022] **BSB.mn**

Mobile application of BSB.MN for e-commerce of online shopping and delivery service. Released the mobile application in 2021.11.01 into both App store and Google Play store.

[01/10/2022 - 01/12/2022] ISU Mongolia

Mobile application of mobile portal application for parents of students and employees of "International School of Ulaanbaatar". The corresponding application is for managing various kinds of activity in the school.

The application is being reviewed by the Apple App store and Google Play store to be published.

[01/06/2022 - 01/09/2022] **G-power monitoring**

Mobile application of monitoring for consumers of power supply company, named "G-power". The corresponding application is for monitoring and surveillance of power consumption of their activity.

The application is being reviewed by the Apple App store and Google Play store to be published.

Togloom Trade

E-game item selling website.

Link: https://togloom.trade/

Dynamic Survey platform

Developed a dynamoic survey form platform in Sliim framework (php) duriging internship in And Systems

CREATIVE WORKS

[16/10/2020 - 18/10/2020] And Systems Hackathon 2020 (awarded 1st place)

Participated and won 1st place in the competition of building a new platform within 2 days as a team. During the competition, our team innovated a new idea of an extension for *Visual studio* code editor and developed the extension, which gives the opportunity to manage all job tasks for developers in their code editor, the result is that developers have no need of entering another task management tool. I contributed my ideas and worked on the development of the extension.

[17/05/2019 - 19/05/2019] LendMN Open Platform Hackathon 2019 (awarded 2nd place)

Participated and won 2nd place in the competition of building a new platform within 2 days as a team consisting of 4 people. During the competition, our team innovated and developed a new idea for an e-sport game item-selling platform. The platform gives game players the opportunity to exchange their game items without fraud, and it prevents scammers. I contributed my ideas and worked on the frontend development of the platform.



Link: https://ikon.mn/n/1kvt

HONOURS AND AWARDS

[11/12/2018] Certified Information Technology Professionals (IP) /MNIP18A0009/ Awarding institution: ITP

EC /Information Technology Professionals Examination Council/

Information Technology Passport Examination - successfully passed

[28/10/2019] Certified Information Technology Professionals (FE) /MNFE19A0008/ Awarding institution: IT

PEC /Information Technology Professionals Examination Council/

Fundamental Information Technology Engineer Examination - successfully passed

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Playing volleyball - former local team member

Ice Skating - Beginner, self educating

Making handcraft furniture

Knitting & Crocheting

Acrylic painting

DRIVING LICENCE

Cars: B







MNIP18A0009 This is to certify that

YESUN-ERDENE Jargalsaikhan

has successfully passed the Information Technology Passport Examination

Examination date: 28/10/2018

Certified Information Technology Professional (IP)

HINBAT Baatarjav Chairman Communications and Information Technology Authority SODNOMDAMBA Tserendori General director National Information Technology Park

Issued on 11/12/2018 Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia

ITPEC Certificate II







Certificate

This is to certify that

YESUN-ERDENE Jargalsaikhan

has successfully passed the Fundamental Information Technology Engineer Examination

Examination date: 27/10/2019

Certified Information Technology Professional (FE)

AT Baatarjav Chairman Communications and Information Technology Authority TSOGTGEREL Erkhembayar Director National Information

Technology Park

Issued on 28/11/2019 Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia